M. L. Parrish Collection of Victorian Novelists, 1806-1958 (bulk 1830s-1930s ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Author Files, 1734-1975; 35 boxes (34 partial)
  - Trollope, Frances Eleanor Ternan, 1835-1913 (second wife of Thomas Adolphus Trollope), undated; 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Trollope, Frances Milton, 1780-1863 (wife of Thomas Anthony Trollope), undated; 4 folders (4 partial)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Letters to Richard Bentley, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Letters to Thomas Adolphus Trollope, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Letters to and about Mrs. Trollope, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Trollope, Henry Merivale, 1846-1926; portion of 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Trollope, Rose Heseltine, 1821-1917; portion of 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Trollope, Theodosia Garrow, 1825-1865 (first wife of Thomas Adolphus Trollope), portion of 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Trollope, Thomas Adolphus, 1810-1892 (elder brother of Anthony Trollope), 6 folders (2 partial)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Letters to Edward Herries, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Letters to his daughter Beatrice ("Bice"), undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Letters to Rev. H. Blackstone Williams, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Letters addressed to Trollope, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - "William of Wykeham and 'Cy pres'", undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Trollope, Thomas Anthony, 1774-1835; 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Papers, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Trollope Family, undated; 1 folder
    - Correspondence and biographical sketches, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Vezin, Hermann, 1903; 3 boxes
    - Night and Morning: a play in 5 acts from Bulwer Lytton's novel, 1903; 3 boxes
      - Typescript with manuscript changes, 1903; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Typescript, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Walker, Frederick, 1840-1875; 1 folder
    - Letters to Joseph Swain, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Wheelwright, Frances, 1843; 1 folder
    - Exercise book and report card, 1843; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Whyte-Melville, George John, 1821-1878; 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Wills, William Henry, 1810-1880; 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Winter, William, 1836-1917; 1 folder
    - "In Memory of Wilkie Collins" (poem) and miscellaneous correspondence, undated; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Winterich, John T., 1928; 1 folder
    - ALS to William Duncan, 1928 September 30; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Wood, Ellen Price, 1814-1887; 2 folders (2 partial)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Letters to Frederic Chapman, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Woolf, Benjamin Edward, 1836-1901; portion of 1 folder
    - Poor Jo: Autograph Ms. of a Drama in 5 Acts from Charles Dickens' Bleak House, 1876 November; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Wordsworth, Christopher, 1807-1885; portion of 1 folder
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901; portions of 3 boxes
    - ALS to Mr. Bauer, 1893 June 28, and miscellaneous papers, 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 4A)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1 of 2), 85 letters, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (2 of 2), 96 letters, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Letters to Sir Walter Besant, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Letters addressed to Miss Yonge, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - "Aunt Charlotte's evenings at home", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - "Cameos from English History", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - The Carbonels: chapters 1-9, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - The Carbonels: chapters 10-18, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - The Carbonels: chapters 19-27, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The Constable's Tower: chapters 1-6, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - The Constable's Tower: chapters 7-16, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - The Constable's Tower: chapters 17-23, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - The Cook and the Captive: chapters 1-7, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - The Cook and the Captive: chapters 8-16, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - The Cook and the Captive: chapters 17-25, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - The Cross Roads: chapters 1-8, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - The Cross Roads: chapters 9-16, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - The Cross Roads: chapters 17-23, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - "The Fair Maids of February", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Albert, Prince Consort of England: chapters 1-2, undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - A Reputed Changeling: Preface, undated; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - The Three Brides: Chapter XXXI, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - The Wardship of Steepcoombe: Chapters 1-7, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - The Wardship of Steepcoombe: Chapters 8-15, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - The Wardship of Steepcoombe: Chapters 16-24, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Series 3: Author Portraits, 1780-1995; portions of 3 boxes
  Consists of individual author folders containing photographs (carte-de-visite and cabinet; some autographed) and postcards of, and article clippings relating to, the authors, as well as miscellaneous ephemera. Arranged alphabetically by author.
  Note: The following folders of "Author Portraits, etc." are referred to by Alexander D. Wainwright, former curator of the Parrish Collection, as his author "iconography files." See list appended at end of this section for additional author portraits (Dickens, Hardy, Stevenson, Thackeray, and Anthony Trollope) currently located in the Taylor Room and elsewhere in the Library.
  - Ainsworth, William Harrison, 1805-1882; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes one photo and several portraits; the original Ainsworth portrait (oil on canvas) by Daniel Maclise hangs over the fireplace in the Parrish Room, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Barrie, Sir James Matthew, Bart, 1860-1937; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes a few portraits, as well as photos of Barrie's father and mother and of the Barrie cottage in Kirriemuir, Scotland, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Black, William, 1841-1898; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes eight carte-de-visite and cabinet photo cards and several other portraits, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Brontë, Charlotte, 1816-1855; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes a few portraits of Charlotte Brontë; four cabinet photo cards of, and many postcards relating to, the Brontë family; and photos depicting scenes in and around Haworth, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Collins, Wilkie, 1824-1889; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes six carte-de-visite photo cards and four cabinet photo cards; numerous other portraits; and four, small, engraved prints of paintings by his father, William, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Craik, Dinah Maria (Mulock), 1826-1887; portion of 1 folder
    - One photograph and a few portraits, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - De la Ramée, Louise (Ouida), 1839-1908; portion of 1 folder
    - One cabinet photo card and two prints engraved from it., undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes over forty portraits of Dickens, from youth to old age; three carte-de-visite, one cabinet photo card and other photos of varying sizes; and portraits of the prototypes of Dickens' literary characters, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Disraeli, Benjamin, Earl of Beaconsfield, 1804-1881; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes one cabinet photo and three carte-de-visite photo cards and other photos, and several other portraits, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Dodgson, Charles Lutwidge (Lewis Carroll), 1832-1898; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes two photographs of Carroll and a few other portraits; photostats of the table of contents lists in the Parrish Collection's C. L. Dodgson's Photograph Albums 1-3, the Holiday album, and separate photographs, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Du Maurier, George Louis Palmella Busson, 1834-1896; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes one etching based on a portrait sketch by Du Maurier; and various portraits relating to Trilby, Du Maurier's 1894 novel that was dramatized for the London stage in 1895 (see Box 100 for his pencil study for Trilby ), undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Eliot, George, pseud. (Marian Cross, née Evans), 1819-1880; 1 folder
    - Includes two cabinet cards and several other portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5a)
  - Faithfull, Emily, 1835-1895; 1 folder
    - Includes one portrait from a collection titled "Some Women's Shadows" and several other portraits with articles in various publications, 1864-1895, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5b)
  - Furniss, Harry, 1854-1925; 1 folder
    - Photograph of Furniss inscribed to Major Pond, signed by Furniss, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 5c)
  - Gaskell, Elizabeth Cleghorn (Stevenson), 1810-1865; portion of 1 folder
    - One photograph, one pen-and-ink drawing, copies of one portrait, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Includes "St. Valentine’s Day. 1864": a mock-valentine sent to Gaskell, apparently by her Publisher George Smith, of Smith, Elder & Co. A pen-and-ink drawing, approx. 10" square, with central scene surrounded by 19 additional scenes, and a bottom panel of eight lines of rhymed text pleading for more copy. The central picture shows Elizabeth Gaskell in a farmyard, bearing a milkmaid’s yoke and looking at a cow, whilst (almost surreptitiously) handing a manuscript to a kneeling George Smith. This is surrounded by the9 smaller images, presumably illustrating Cousin Phillis, rather like a medieval stained-glass window or a panel of a saint’s life. In fact Gaskell, who is said to have much preferred dealing with Smith rather than the editor, did contribute further to the Cornhill: she was already planning her next – and, as it turned out, final – novel, Wives and Daughters, which began to appear in the August number of the same year.
  - Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes several portraits of Hardy and photos of his birthplace and Max Gate homes (see oversize Box 100, Folder 15 for one additional photo portrait), undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Hughes, Thomas, 1822-1896; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes five carte-de-visite and other photos; plus several other portraits (see Box 104 for two additional caricature portraits of Hughes), undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Kingsley, Charles, 1819-1875; 1 folder
    - Two cabinet and fourteen carte-de-visite photo cards and many other photos; plus several other portraits (see Box 100 for one additional photo portrait)*, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lever, Charles James, 1806-1872; 1 folder
    - One carte-de-visite photograph and two other portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Lytton, Edward George Earle Lytton Bulwer-Lytton, 1st Baron, 1803-1877; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes seven carte-de-visite photographs and seven other photos; one group portrait of Lord Bulwer Lytton, Lord Macauley, T. Carlyle, Makepeace Thackeray, Charles Dickens, Geo. Mac-Donald, A. J. Froude, Wilkie Collins, and Anthony Trollope; and numerous other portraits of Lytton, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Maxwell, Mary Elizabeth (Braddon), 1837-1915; portion of 1 folder
    - Two carte-de-visite photographs, two photo postcards, and two other photos, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Meredith, George, 1828-1909; portion of 1 folder
    - Three portraits, including one mounted on cardboard, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Reade, Charles, 1814-1884; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes a news clipping containing a "Letter of Charles Reade to his brother in India" and the wording of the inscription on Reade's tombstone; photograph and negative of a portrait in oil bequeathed by Reade to Harper & Brothers; two cabinet cards and two other photos of Reade; and numerous other portraits (see Box 100, Folder 18 for one caricature portrait), undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes photograph and negative of the bronze plaque by Augustus Saint-Gaudens and a negative of the Stevenson portrait by Count Girolamo Nerli; four carte-de-visite photographs; commemorative postage stamps issued by Western Samoa (site of Stevenson's Vaillima residence and tomb); and several other portraits., undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863; portion of 1 folder
    - Includes four carte-de-visite photos; photos of Marble Bust of Thackeray when a Boy; E. S. Wells Kerr/Photographs to illustrate Letters of Anne Thackeray Ritchie, London, John Murray, 1924; and numerous other portraits, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Trollope, Anthony, 1815-1882; portion of 1 folder
    - One cabinet photo and ten carte-de-visite photo cards and several other photos; six negatives of photo portraits; and numerous other portraits (see Box 100, Folder 19 for one caricature portrait), undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Trollope, Frances (Milton), 1780-1863; 1 folder
    - Nine copies of one portrait, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Wood, Ellen (Price), 1814-1887; 1 folder
    - Two copies of an original London theatre program of East Lynne and a few portraits, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901; 1 folder
    - Two cabinet photo cards and several other photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Additional Author Portraits located in the Taylor Room, 1811-1995; 1 item
    - Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870; 1 item
      - Charcoal portrait by Samuel Laurence (1812-1884), 28.5 x 22.75 in., framed, [1860?], undated; 1 item
      - Lithographed portrait in colors, after E. Goodwyn Lewis, signed by Dickens on the mount, 23 x 18 inches, 1869; 1 item
    - Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928; 1 item
      - Signed charcoal portrait by Reginald Grenville Eves (1876-1941), 25 x 21 in., framed, 1923; 1 item
      - Signed oil portrait by Reginald Grenville Eves (1876-1941), 22.5 x 19 in, undated; 1 item
      - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863; 1 item
      - Plaster statuette by Sir Joseph Edgar Boehm (1834-1890), Bucciani & Co.(London), 20.5 in, 1860; 1 item
    - Trollope, Anthony, 1815-1882; 1 item
      - Signed portrait by Samuel Laurence (1812-1884), in charcoal, pencil, and chalk, 33.5 x 27 in. framed, 1864; 1 item
      - Statuette by Gertrude Fass (1909- ), in bronze, 16.5" high, on black micarta base, from the workshop of Domenico Ranieri (New York) -- #4 of 250 castings worldwide, 1995; 1 item
  - Oversize Item in the University Librarian's Office, 1850-1894; 1 item
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894; 1 item
      - Signed bronze circular medallion by Augustus Saint-Gaudens (1848-1907) of Stevenson reading in bed, propped by pillows and holding a cigarette, 34.5 in. diameter, in octagonal frame, 1887; 1 item
- Series 4: Parrish Correspondence, 1913-1944; 39 boxes (36 partial)
  Consists of Parrish's correspondence with book collectors and dealers, family members of the Victorian novelists he collected, scholars, etc., filed alphabetically by correspondent and/or subject.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
  - A (General), dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Academy of Natural Sciences, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Adams, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Adler, Elmer, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Admiralty Island, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Alaska, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Aldus, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Allen, J. A., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - American Autograph Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - American Art Assoc. - Anderson Galleries, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - American Book Company, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Amory, Mrs. Harcourt, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Antiquarian Book Company, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Argosy Book Stores, Inc, 1930-1937; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Argosy Book Stores, 1938-1944; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Argus Book Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Arlington Book Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Athenaeum of Philadelphia, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Ba - Bm (General), dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Bo - Bz (General), dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Backus, Edgar, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Barrington-Brown, P. R., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Bates, George, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Becker, Florence, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Beinecke, Edwin J., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin, Walter R., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Bennett Book Studios, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Berlin National Bank, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Berolzheimer, Alfred C., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Beyer, Barnet J., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Bibliophile, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Biddle, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Blackburn, Philip C., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Blackburn, Philip C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11A)
  - Blackwell, B. H., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Blackwood, William & Sons, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Blanck, Jacob, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Block, Andrew, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Bodley Book Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Bone, James, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Bonnell, Henry H., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Book Farm, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - The Book Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Brentano's, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Brick Row Book Shop, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Bright, Robert S., undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - British Museum, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Broadbent, N. M., undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Brontë, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Brooks, Philip, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Brown, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Brown, William, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Browning, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1930-1931; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1932; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1933; portion of 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1934-1942; 9 folders (Box 52, Folder 1-9)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1943-1944; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Brussel, I. R., 1943-1944; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Bumpus, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - C (General), dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Calhoun, Philo C., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Campion & Co., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Carman's, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Book Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Carroll, Lewis, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - L. Carroll Catalogue, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Carter, John, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Cavanaugh, C. W., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Chao, Y. R., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Chase National Bank, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Chaucer Head Book Shop, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Cheston, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Chew, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Chiswick Book Shop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Christ Church, Oxford, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Hartley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Clotworthy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Colbeck, Norman, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Colbeck, Radford & Co., Ltd, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Collectors' Bookshop, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Collins, Wilkie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - The Colophon, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Colophon Club, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Coolidge, Miss Bertha, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Coykendall, Fred, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Craik, Mrs. D. M., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Cutler, B. D., dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - D (General), dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Dauber & Pine, dates not examined; portion of 1 folder (Box 55, Folder 9)